Welcome to a new series on the channel
recreating Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but low calorie and high protein. We're
starting off with what is supposedly
Dairy Queen's most popular blizzard, the
turtle pecan cluster. Let me show you
how to make it. To start off, you're
going to need 400 g of a fat-free milk.
I always use the one from Fairife. Then
about a teaspoon of vanilla bean paste,
40 to 45 grams of a sugar substitute,
1/4 teaspoon of salt, 1/4 teaspoon of
zantham gum, and then you're just going
to blend that all together and throw it
in the freezer for at least 16 hours.
Once it's completely frozen, you can
take it out and run under hot water for
about a minute. And then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. It might come out a little bit
powdery. Mine was pretty good, but just
to make sure, I scraped down the sides
and then hollowed out a hole in the
middle. And then this is where the
chocolate comes into play. I got 15 g of
chocolate melted with 2 g of coconut oil
and then we're going to drizzle that
down the center and then run it on the
mixing setting. This makes the most
delicious chocolate chips. Way better
than just adding in chocolate chips. It
does add a step, I know, but 100% worth
it. Also, can someone tell me how the
turtle pecan cluster blizzard is the
most popular one? I've literally never
seen anyone order it. But anyways, we're
going to top it with some caramel and
then some chopped pecans and then you're
good to go. This thing is amazing. My
friends said it was easily a top five
recipe that they've tried. Comment what
flavor I should try to recreate from
Dairy Queen next.